It seems there was
a student general meeting the other day.
I heard
Masachika and the heiress of
Taniyama Heavy Industries were involved.
Yes.
She was your rival
until the very last moment
in junior high after all.
I thought she was more capable.
But it seems she left
in the middle of the meeting.
I'm sure she has her reasons.
In any case,
Masachika's reputation has been boosted.
Listen up.
No matter who your opponent is,
you must not lose.
Grandfather, I understand.
You may not be as talented as Masachika,
but
you know the responsibility
that comes with competency.
In that regard,
he's beyond help.
He has the greatest talent of anyone
and a uniquely privileged environment,
but he gave up his responsibility.
That's why you must never
lose to someone like him.
Do you understand, Yuki?
Yes, Grandfather.
Yuki?
Mother,
is something wrong?
Are you and Masachika
getting along well?
Yes, of course.
I see.
Well,
is something wrong with my brother?
No, it's nothing.
You have a Chinese class later, right?
Yes, it's a remote lesson today.
Do your best.
Yes.
Ayano.
Yes, Mistress Yuki?
Let me hold you.
Yes, as you wish.
Good, I'm all better now.
Is that all?
Thank you.
Oh, dear.
Boobs really are great, aren't they?
Yo, Kuze.
Last week's general meeting was amazing.
When I first heard Taniyama's argument,
I thought it was over.
Which part of it was your strategy?
Anyway, let me put down my stuff first.
Good morning, Alya.
Good morning.
Well, her reaction is the same as usual.
Alya.
These guys want to hear
about your heroics last week.
What?
Well then, just ask Alya for the details.
The gacha event is waiting for me.
Kujou.
Did you come up with the speech
at the general meeting last week?
What?
Well, you could say that.
It took me by surprise.
I didn't know you were
so good at giving speeches.
Thank you.
You didn't ask any questions.
Was that your strategy?
Yes.
That's what we decided in advance.
Then, why did Kuze barge in midway?
I didn't expect that either.
By the way,
Taniyama ran away midway.
How dare she run away
from the challenge she started?
That's so lame.
Kuze, a minute, please.
Come to think of it,
the student council needs extra hands.
Sorry, I'll talk to you later.
So what's the matter?
You don't want to hear Taniyama
being criticized so harshly?
Because Taniyama…
Indeed,
we know why Taniyama did those things.
But we won it fair and square
so it's not our fault.
No matter what is said,
we don't have to worry about Taniyama.
Don't we?
I know that.
But we didn't actually win.
Then what do you want to do?
If we want to restore
Taniyama's reputation,
then our victory
in the general meeting wouldn't count.
I know that too.
Anyway, that's about it
from a rational perspective.
But it doesn't really matter.
What?
What's important is what you want to do.
Of course, I want to help Taniyama.
But that's…
I know.
Let's do it then.
What? Is that okay?
Yes.
Rather than holding on to it now,
it's better to settle things
and welcome the closing ceremony.
I'm sorry.
I said something troublesome.
Don't worry about it.
Didn't I tell you?
I'll support you.
Kuze.
There's someone over there.
Come closer.
But…
It's totally like a rom-com.
As a competent junior,
I should act like nothing happened
and leave at a time like this.
What's going on?
Did I also trigger a rom-com event?
This is no good.
What's no good? Everything, of course.
At this point,
I have no choice but to forcefully change
the course of the event!
So how long are you two going to hide?
President, Sarashina.
What?
I'm sorry.
We missed our timing to come out.
That's right.
We were just looking
for something that fell on the floor.
Well then,
let's just pretend that neither of us saw
nor heard anything this time, okay?
Okay.
You're right. Let's do just that.
It's a deal then.
Let's go, Alya.
Well, I…
I still have other things to do.
Hey, Nonoa.
Don't you think Fymel's
new release is so cute?
It doesn't really click with me.
I see.
If you don't like it, then forget it.
Such a powerful social presence.
I can't even get close to her.
Forget about that, Nonoa.
Can you come
to my house party this Sunday?
But the test is coming up.
Well then, come over
and revise for the test.
What?
Don't you think
you've been a bit cold lately?
No… I'm just kidding.
A house party?
Definitely count me in.
Great!
Hey, if Nonoa's going, I want to go too.
Kuzecchi, do you need anything?
Yeah, something like that.
I see.
You can't talk about it here?
Yes, let's go somewhere else.
Okay.
So?
If you want to confess, I'll accept it.
But that's not why you're here, right?
Yeah.
Wait, you're willing
to accept my confession?
Well, I'm single now.
Besides, I don't hate you.
No, don't date someone you don't hate.
Date properly with someone you like.
But I've never been
in a relationship with someone I like.
Hey, that statement sounds a bit off.
It can't be helped.
I don't really know what love is.
I don't mean
to criticize your views on love,
but I think you shouldn't
degrade yourself.
Sayacchi said that to me too.
But she also slapped me when she said it.
Seriously?
She would slap her friend?
Well, it was a special circumstance.
Anyway, let's get back to the topic.
What do you want?
A lot of people are talking
about Taniyama, right?
I'm wondering
if we can cool things down a bit.
Does that bother you, Kuzecchi?
It bothers my partner.
I see.
That's very kind of you.
So?
Why are you telling me this?
I'm considered your enemy, aren't I?
Enemy?
I'm sure you noticed, Kuzecchi.
I sent shills to instigate the audience.
Of course, I did.
You sent your friends as shills.
How could you do something
that might cost you all your friends?
To be honest,
I'm not too attached to my friends
other than Sayacchi.
Even if I lose them, it doesn't bother me.
I'm curious about something.
People like Taniyama
who hides her emotions deep inside
are the type you find hardest
to understand, right?
Why are you so attached to her?
It's the opposite actually.
I'm interested in her
and want to be with her
because I don't understand her.
Is that so?
I'm sure you understand
this feeling too, Kuzecchi.
When you see a brilliance that you lack,
you can't help but yearn for it.
Then…
as a fellow twisted person who yearns
for an honest and dazzling partner,
let's come up with a wicked scheme.
Well, it's not a wicked scheme per se.
To put it simply,
I'd like you to make up a plausible reason
for Taniyama fleeing midway
and spread it as a rumor.
So you want people to think
that she didn't run away from the enemy?
Is that okay?
Your victory could become controversial.
I know.
All right.
She was my partner anyway.
It makes more sense for me
to take care of it.
Then it's a deal.
Thanks.
Is this one of those situations?
If we were in a manga,
she'd call her secret henchmen
and give out orders like
"Chase after them"
and "Don't get caught."
Ayano.
Yes, Master Masachika?
Why are you here?
Because I think you called me.
Hey, don't forget about me, Brother.
No. Why are you guys here?
No reason.
I found out you were trying
to make contact with our enemy, Ms. Nonoa.
So I got ahead of you
and hid under the desk.
Under the desk again?
So what's the real reason?
We wanted to roleplay
a secret meeting in an empty classroom.
I didn't expect you
to start a real secret meeting.
Seriously, what are you doing?
Kuze, are you here?
Alya?
Did you misunderstand something?
What misunderstanding?
The three of you grew up together.
It's not strange for you to play together.
I'll get going now. Have fun.
Alya.
What? I can't believe you left me out.
Bro.
Judging by her face, I'm sure this is it.
"I made lunch for Kuze
to thank him for helping me
at the general meeting."
"But where is he?"
And then, she searched the whole
school premises to find this place.
Don't make up your own stories!
That was a different guy
from last time, right?
Is that so?
Anyway, he's my boyfriend now.
A kiss won't make a difference, right?
Don't degrade yourself.
Take better care of yourself!
You didn't have to get so mad.
Nonoa, you're finally back.
What did you two talk about?
We were just talking about Sayacchi.
She took the day off.
Kuzecchi wanted to ask what happened.
Taniyama took the day off?
Is it because she lost the debate?
No, no.
It's actually because of me.
Speaking of which,
Sayacchi gave up on the debate
because of me too.
What?
What do you mean?
Actually, at the general meeting that day,
I planted some shills in the audience.
Sayacchi found out about it.
Something like that.
I just happened
to run into Yuki and Ayano.
You don't look convinced at all.
That's not true.
Actually, you don't have
to hide it from me.
Isn't it good to be close
to childhood friends?
By the way,
do you want to study together
after school today?
Are you kidding me?
Hey, that's too rude.
Excuse me, Alya?
What is it?
Don't you think you're a little too close?
Is that a problem?
No, it's not.
It's fine.
As long as no one sees us…
Oh, my.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't knock.
Little Sister!
Are you studying for the exam?
If you don't mind, can we join you?
Yes, I do mind.
Alya.
What do you think
about what Yuki said?
Sure.
No reason to turn them down.
I see.
Thank you.
I wanted it to be just the two of us.
Seriously, this girl.
Don't say something so adorable!
You've only been looking
at the answer sheet.
Are you really studying for the exam?
It's a waste of time to ponder
on a question you don't understand.
If you have time for that,
it's faster to memorize all the solutions.
Then you can't apply it properly.
It's fine.
Masachika has always been like this.
Right, Ayano?
Yes.
Master Masachika
has always studied like this.
Ayano, is there anything
you don't understand?
No.
Actually, there is.
Where?
It's okay.
There's no need to trouble you
with such a trivial matter.
Don't be shy.
I won't look down on you.
No.
At a time like this, I'd rather you
mercilessly call me "a useless person."
I won't say that.
I… see.
Why do you look disappointed?
Hey, are you guys really
just childhood friends?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
Why…
It's just that
you say you're childhood friends,
but the way you interact seems distant.
Everyone, thanks for the hard work.
Masha's black tea is the best.
Oh, my. What's this?
I think it's a book
that Sarashina confiscated.
A FOOLPROOF GUIDE
TO STARTING HYPNOSIS
Alya, try to hypnotize me.
I don't want to.
What? Why?
I want to experience hypnosis too.
I want to try it too.
I told you, I won't.
Then you try it, Kuze.
What? Me?
It's because Alya is so cold.
Well, I guess that's fine.
The first step is… hypnosis induction?
I can't wait!
Let's see.
Okay, "please look at this finger."
Finger?
That's what it says.
I see.
"Your consciousness will start to fade."
"And please keep looking at this finger."
"Okay."
"You're losing consciousness."
"After I clap my hands,
you'll fall into the world of dreams."
"Three, two, one, asleep."
What? Masha?
Masha?
Did it really work?
All right, cut it out.
Masha?
Anyway,
let me undo the hypnosis first.
Let's see.
"When I touch your shoulder,
the hypnosis will be broken."
"One, two, wake up."
Well, Kuze, what's next?
What?
Come on.
Doesn't it say to clap
after you raise your finger?
No…
What? Don't you remember?
What? Remember what?
Masha.
Seriously, stop pretending.
Well then, Alya.
Why don't you try getting
hypnotized by Masachika too?
-What?
If you feel the effect,
it'll remove your doubts, right?
All right. I'm ready.
Are we really doing this?
Don't ask.
I'll put an end to this farce in no time.
Then, "please look at this finger."
She's so gullible.
By the way,
why was Masha hypnotized too?
Who knows?
Seriously?
We can do so much erotic stuff.
Even so, don't say it out loud!
It's time for an otaku quiz.
Here's the question.
A beautiful woman
is accidentally hypnotized.
When it comes to the first cue,
what is it usually?
Let her regress to a baby!
Make her more open
and take off her clothes!
Well…
Maybe make her tell me
some embarrassing secrets?
You said to make her more open.
Isn't that too general?
Regressing to a baby
is too aggressive, right?
Ayano's suggestion.
It's not bad,
but it's a bit too weak.
In that sense,
my suggestion to make her more open
was absolutely the correct answer.
Besides, she might also reveal
some embarrassing secrets.
You even considered my answer.
Amazing, Mistress Yuki.
All right. I win by majority vote.
Alya.
Masha.
Your personalities will gradually open up
and you'll lose your wits.
Strip your bodies and minds naked.
What? What?
Did it really work?
What?
Hey, Yuki.
Why am I being patted endlessly here?
There, there.
Who knows? I wonder why?
Hey, look over here, you criminal!
I can't believe it wasn't Masachika,
but Masha who established a harem.
You're shocked about the weirdest thing.
There, there.
Well, Masha.
Can you let go of me now?
No.
You can't?
So annoying.
It's in the way.
Alya? What do you want?
That's the morning look of a skilled
but lazy-at-home office lady!
I get you!
No! Wait!
Why are they all stripping?
Come to think of it,
I think I ordered them
to gradually open up
and strip their bodies and minds naked.
Let's see.
Well then, when I touch your shoulder,
the hypnosis will be broken.
One, two, wake up.
Hey, isn't it still in effect?
What?
Well then, when I touch your shoulder,
the hypnosis will be broken.
One, two, wake up.
Oh, no. I can't undo it either.
Seriously?
Wait, what should we do?
Masha.
I'm done with my stuff.
What's going on?
Sarashina.
Well, it's like this.
I tried the hypnosis in the book just now,
but I couldn't undo it.
Excuse my rudeness.
Hold on.
What did you just do?
What? I just did a reset.
What?
That's strange.
Why am I lying on the sofa?
Oh my?
Well,
I know you must be confused now.
But you should tidy yourself up first.
What?
Tidy up?
What is going on?
Oh, no!
By the way, Kuze,
you saw everything, right?
Do you need a reset from me?